《异形大战铁血战士2：安魂曲》
好了 慢慢来
Okay, now, take your time.
可以了
There you go.
爸爸 爸爸 在上面
Dad! Dad! It's up here!
慢点 山姆 慢点
Slow down, Sam, slow down.
哇
Wow…
是啊 我们 我们得去通知警长
Yeah, we're… we're gonna show this to the sheriff.
怎么回事？好了 我们走
What's happening? Come on, let's go.
快点 走
Come on… go!
快点 跑 跑 跑
Move it. Go, go, go!
快点 山姆
Go, Sam…
山姆 你没事吧？
Sam, you all right?
低头
Stay down.
爸爸 我害怕
Dad, I'm scared.
小心
Watch out!
爸爸
Dad
爸爸？
Dad?
还好吧 达拉斯？
How you doin', Dallas?
艾迪
Eddie.
好啦 我带你一段吧
Come on, I'll give you a ride.
我以前都是坐在后面的
Yeah, I usually ride in the back.
我记得有几次
I seem to remember you being with me
也是你在前面开车吧
a couple of those times.
能问你点东西？
Ask you something?
你 呃 你后悔吗？
You, uh… You regret what you did?
不
No.
怎么了 你觉得我应该后悔？
Why? You thought I would?
我只是觉得三年该够长了
I think three years is a long time.
怎么？你在雇人？
You got work lined up?
你找到工作了吗？
Why? You hiring?
我说服别人够麻烦的了
I've got enough trouble convincing people
这是我的工作
I belong on the job.
不过 我愿意跑遍整个镇子来找你
But I'll ask around town for you.
我很感激
I appreciate it.
你 见到我弟弟了吗？
You, uh… seen my brother?
实际上 我见他见得都烦了
Actually, I been seeing him too much.
大佬比萨店 需要点什么吗？
Pizza One. How can I help you?
记得带帽子
Gotta wear the hat.
祖 你让我们带帽子
Drew, the only reason you make us wear a hat
仅仅是因为当你以前当司机的时候
is 'cause some manager made you wear a hat
某些经理要求你带帽子
when you were a driver.
听着 你能得到这份工作
Look, the only reason you got this job
仅仅是因为你的监护顾问
is because your guidance counselor begged me
求着我给你的
to give it to you.
是啊 我知道她的性感
Yeah, I'm sure the fact that she's hot
跟这没有一点关系 对吧？
had nothing to do with that, huh?
水冠街1427号
1427 Watercrest.
我不能送这个货
I can't make that delivery.
让白瑞去送吧
Have Barry do it.
这里不讲民主
This is not a democracy.
要么送过去 要么走人
Make the run or you're fired.
记得带帽子
And wear the hat!
巡逻31号大卫报告
This is R- 31- David
正在对4号下水道枢纽例行检查
investigating a 10- 66 at sewer junction four.
收到 巡逻31号大卫
Copy that, R- 31- David.
哈瑞 跟你说过多少次了 叫你这些人不要到这儿来
Harry… we keep telling you guys to stay out of here…
你却老跑回来
and you keep coming back.
我不想这样做 不过我必须得把你带回去
I hate to do this, but I'm gonna have to take you in.
让我找找我的狗吧
Let me just get my dog.
布斥？
Butch?
布斥
Butch!
过来 孩子
Come here, boy.
这是什么？
What is that?
天呐
Jesus!
警长 警长
Uh… Sheriff, Sheriff…
嗨 瑞奇
Hey, Ricky.
嗨 杰西
Hi, Jesse.
进来吧
Come on in.
我给你拿点喝的？
Can I get you something to drink?
不用了 谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
装备不错啊 瑞奇
That's a cute outfit, Ricky.
是啊 是不是圣诞提前到了？
Yeah, isn't Halloween in October?
至少我知道谁订了「腊肠情人」
At least now I know who ordered the "Sausage Lover's."
哦
Ooh!
我的钱包在厨房里
My purse is in the kitchen.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
他真是个混蛋
He can be such an asshole.
是啊 没错 你一直都知道怎么结交他们
Yeah, well… you've always known how to pick 'em, Jess.
我可以告诉你个小秘密
Well, I'll let you in on a little secret:
我准备解雇他了
I'm getting ready to fire him.
解雇他
Fire him.
很有趣
That's funny.
我要付你多少钱？
So what do I owe you?
恩 53.50圆
Uh… $53.50.
别找了
Keep it.
谢谢
Thanks.
等会见
I'll see you later.
来啊
Come on!
戴尔 戴尔 住手
Dale! Dale, stop it!
就为了一个微笑 值得吗？
Was that laugh you got worth it?
不回答？
Huh? No answer?
戴尔 让他走
Dale, leave him alone!
把钥匙给我
Give me my keys.
看看你能不能在30分钟内 找到钥匙 蠢货
If you can find 'em in 30 minutes or less, asshole.
走
Let's go.
婊子
Bitch.
比萨小子
Pizza boy.
回家 杰西
Let's go, Jesse!
试着发现更多的信息
Try and get more information
找到可能的伤员 并且报告是否需要救护车
and call about possible injuries and whether medical is needed.
救护车 死者 （美国警方无线电用语）
14-29.
雷 你发现了什么？
Ray, you find anything?
没有
Nothing.
有人把车停在岔路口吗？
Anyone parked at the turnout?
巴迪·本森的卡车
Buddy Benson's truck.
天呐 艾迪
Jesus, Eddie.
他一般都和孩子一起出来的
He usually goes out with his kid.
爸爸？
Dad?
嘿
Hey!
我真想你
I missed you so much.
她长这么大了
She's so big!
是啊
I know.
嘿
Hey!
上帝 我真不敢相信你回来了
God. I can't believe you're home!
好久了
It's been so long.
要我帮你吗？
You want some help?
这些是给我的？
Are these for me?
你不喜欢？
You don't like them?
什么 你开玩笑吗？
What, are you kidding me?
这么酷
Those are so cool.
等会我们来教你怎么用 好吗？
We'll show you how they work later, okay?
好吧
Okay.
好了
All right.
好
你的门有问题吗？
You got a problem with the door?
你什么时候回来的？
When'd you get back?
今天
Today.
你的脸怎么了？
What happened to your face?
等会儿再谈
Talk about it later.
瑞奇
Ricky…
- 嘿 - 我们等会儿再谈
- Hey! - We'll talk about it later.
- 我们现在就谈 - 把手拿开
- Let's talk about it now. - Get your hands off.
把你该死的手拿开
Get your fuckin' hands off me!
你的脸到底怎么了？
What happened to your face?
戴尔·科林斯和他的朋友打了我
Dale Collins and his friends jumped me.
还把我的钥匙扔进下水道
They threw my keys in the sewer.
好吧 把球棒给我
All right, give me the bat.
- 你在这里干什么？- 瑞奇
- What are you doing here… - Ricky…
- 你要干什么？- 我不会再说一遍
- What are you doing?! - I'm not gonna ask…
把那该死的球棒给我
Give me the fuckin' bat.
好啦 我帮你去找钥匙
Come on… I'll help you find your keys.
布斥 闭嘴
Butch, shut up!
哈瑞？
Harry?
最好给我留点
Better save some for me.
哦 老天啊
Oh, my God.
哦 哈瑞
Oh, Harry.
救命
Please!
妈妈
Mom!
很抱歉 你该睡了 甜心
I'm sorry. It's your bedtime, honey.
我还不困呢
I'm not sleepy yet.
茉莉
Molly.
把它放到一边
Put those away.
该睡觉了
It's time for bed.
我爱你
I love you.
我想让爸爸读
I want Dad to read it.
好吧
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
明天早上见
I'll see you in the morning.
好吗？
Okay?
嘿
Hey…
你记得多少次
You remember all those times
你跟我说你很想念妈妈？
you told me how much you missed Mommy?
告诉她 没关系的
It's okay to tell Mommy that.
好的
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
你把她照顾得很好
You've done an amazing job with her.
她一直很想你
She's missed you.
我离开 她生我气
She's angry that I left.
茉莉只是需要点时间
Well, Molly just needs a little time.
也许我犯了个错误
Maybe I made a mistake.
没有 你没有犯错
Hey, no. You didn't make a mistake.
我们只是很想念你
We've just missed you.
我也很想你们 真的
I missed you too. Yeah.
快点
Hurry up.
你想自己来？
You want to do it?
你是家里的罪人
You're the convict in the family.
好笑
Funny.
帮我一下 好吗？
Help me out, all right?
为什么我们不从
Why don't we just climb down
他们扔钥匙的地方爬下去？
from where they threw your keys?
那样杰西就可以看到我满身是屎地爬出来？
So Jesse can see me climb out covered in shit?
不 谢谢
No, thanks.
等一下
Wait a second.
我们会满身是屎？
We're gonna be covered in shit?
拿着
Take this.
这下面真恶心
It's gross down here.
我能想出更恶心的地方
I can think of worse places.
我猜没人在家
Guess nobody's home.
那是个睡椅吗？
Is that a couch?
是的
Yeah.
比咱家的好
It's nicer than ours.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
哦 闻起来像有东西死在这里了
Oh, it smells like something died down here.
你确定是这条路？
You sure this is the right way?
应该就在那上边
This should be it right up here.
就是这个下水道
That's the drain.
检查下
Check down there.
是你的钥匙 混蛋
They're your keys, asshole.
你有手
You got hands.
是 不过我可不打算把手叉到那堆屎里 你自己捞
Yeah, and I'm not sticking 'em in that shit. You do it.
怪你自己吧
Knock yourself out.
跟我说说这个女孩
Tell me about this girl.
哪个女孩？
What girl?
让你屁股挨揍的女孩
The one you got your ass kicked over.
就只是个女孩
It's just a girl.
没人只是为了个一般女孩
No one goes digging around through shit
在屎里面挖东西
over just some girl.
好吗？
Okay?
那他妈是什么玩意？
What the hell was that?
放松 就是只老鼠
Relax. It's just a rat.
那他妈才不是老鼠
It's no fuckin' rat.
好了 检查下那个下水道
All right, check that drain.
我找到了
I got 'em.
走吧
Let's go.
妈的 警长 巴迪的老婆来了
Shit, Sheriff. That's Buddy's wife.
嘿 我们有伴儿了
Hey, we got some company.
- 达西 - 艾迪
- Darcy. - Eddie.
我没收到任何消息
I haven't heard anything.
- 我们正在找他们 - 他们可能受伤了
- We're looking for them. - They could be hurt.
他们也可能正在回家的路上
Or they could be on their way home.
你在浪费时间
You're wasting your time.
好了 伙计们 请回到你的车里去
Okay, folks, please, go back and get in your cars.
艾迪 我的家人在里面
Eddie, my family is out there.
我们会找到他们的 交给我们吧
And we're gonna find them. Let us handle it.
今天晚上你们去寻找 太危险了
It's too dangerous out there for you all to search tonight.
现在开始 我们自己负责了 警长
Around here, we take care of our own, Sheriff.
不管有没有你们 我们都会去找的
We're gonna do the search whether you like it or not.
山姆？
Sam?
雷 往桥那边走
Ray, head towards the bridge.
山姆 你在哪儿？
Sammy, where are you?!
巴迪
Buddy?!
巴迪？
山姆
Sam?!
凯莉 把他们带过来
Kelly, bring 'em in!
你在哪儿 巴迪？
Where are you, Buddy?
山姆？山姆？
Sam? Sam?
巴迪 巴迪
Buddy! Buddy!
巴迪
Buddy!
我们不会扔下你不管的 山姆
We won't stop looking for you, Sammy!
艾迪？
Eddie?
达西 我们明天再来找
Darcy, we'll start up again tomorrow.
我的丈夫和孩子就在里面 某个地方
My husband and my son are out here… somewhere.
他们不会扔下我不管的
They wouldn't stop looking for me.
你觉得是不是
Do you think that…
发生了什么？
something happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
你为什么不回家去 休息一下？
Why don't you go home and get some rest?
走吧 我们需要你的力量
Come on, we need your strength.
好吧
Right.
我们明天早上集合
We're going to regroup tomorrow in the morning.
在晚上找没什么用
We're no good at night here.
雷 有发现吗？
Ray, anything?
没有
Negative.
我将最后一次检查大桥那边
I'm gonna make a final pass by the ridge.
好的 保持联系
All right, keep in touch.
还有 我明天早上再找你
Otherwise, I'll see you in the morning.
所有单位 报告情况
All units, report back.
请原谅 先生
Excuse me, sir.
如果你见到了我丈夫和儿子
If you've seen my husband or my son…
- 好的 - 谢谢你
- Okay. - Thank you.
请原谅
Pardon me.
请看看这个
If I could give you this.
这是我的丈夫和孩子
This is my husband and my son.
请留意一下
Just keep an eye.
- 当然 - 谢谢你们
- Oh, sure. - Thank you.
吉那森小镇因为最近
Gunnison residents have been jolted
一个男子和他孩子的神秘失踪而震动
by the mysterious disappearance of a man and his young son
在昨天的搜救过程中
during a hunting trip yesterday.
巴迪·本森 吉那森镇
Buddy Benson, a repair supervisor
电信公司的高级工程师
for the Gunnison telephone company
还有他的儿子 山姆 并没有回家
and his young son, Sam, never returned home last night.
茉莉？宝贝 过来吃
Molly? Honey, come eat.
工作找的怎么样了？
How's the job hunt going?
破门而入算不算特长？
Is breaking and entering a special skill?
你有什么建议吗？
You got any suggestions?
我听说银行在招人
I hear the bank's hiring.
早啊 警长
Morning, Sheriff.
嘿
Hey.
早
Morning.
巴迪和他的儿子有消息了吗？
Any word on Buddy and his kid?
凯瑞？
Carrie?
请倒点咖啡
Coffee, please.
你们整晚都在找？
You guys have been out all night, huh?
没有 我们两点就停下了
No. We called it off at 2:00 a.m.
雷没有回家？
Ray didn't come home?
艾迪 我以为他跟着你
Eddie, I thought he was out with you.
我打过他的手机
I tried his cell phone.
凯瑞 听我说
Carrie, listen to me.
雷昨天晚上很着急
Ray was pushing real hard last night.
我肯定他还在找
I'm sure he's still looking.
监狱管理那边
Cell reception out there…
他平时都会打的 艾迪
He always calls, Eddie.
雷
Ray!
Ray?!
雷 你在那边吗？
Ray, you down there?
雷？
Ray?
哦 老天啊
Oh, my God.
我不相信这是 雷·亚当姆斯
I can't believe this is Ray Adams.
我也不想相信
I don't want to believe it either.
知道什么能驱使一个人这么干？
Know what it would take for a man to do this?
让一个人 活活剥别人的皮？
For someone to… skin a human being?
没有一点痕迹
There were no tracks.
没有
Nothing.
艾迪 这次太麻烦了
Eddie, you're in over your head.
你打算怎么做？
What are you going to do?
我想出来后 会告诉你的
I'll let you know when I figure it out.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 杰西
Hey, Jesse.
嗨
Hi.
知道吗 在教室你就是用这种眼神看我的
You know, you look at me that same way in class.
是啊 啊 嗯
Yeah, well, uh…
钟表在你背后
the clock's behind you.
什么？
What?
明天你去上课的时候 回头
Tomorrow when you're in class, turn around.
你就能看到
You'll see it.
是啊 我
Yeah, I…
我知道钟在那儿 不过
I know that it's there, but…
我们都知道 你看的不是钟
we both know that's not what you're looking at.
知道吗 你一直不善于说谎
You know, you never were a good liar.
今晚 你想去游泳吗？
Do you want to go swimming tonight?
游泳
Swimming.
在哪儿？
Where?
学校
At school.
来吧 就跟过去一样
Come on, it'll be like old times.
过去 在你有男朋友之前？
Old times like before you had a boyfriend?
是的
Yeah.
不过 实际上 是前男友
And it's ex- boyfriend, actually.
他被解雇了
He's been fired.
那么 今晚？
So, tonight.
10点左右
Around 10:00.
晚上见
See you tonight.
我们正在关门 达西
We're closing out now, Darcy.
等你过来再见了
See you when you get here.
你没事吧
You all right?
如果你想谈谈
If you want to talk…
没事
It's okay.
今晚你可以跟我还有凯西住在一起
You're welcome to stay with me and Cathy tonight.
达西正在赶过来 我跟她一起住
Darcy's coming by… I'm gonna stay with her.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
我们在树林里找到了雷的尸体
We found Ray's body in the woods.
他 嗯 他被活活剥了皮
He was, uh… he was skinned alive.
你觉得这跟
Think it's got something to do with…
巴迪和他的孩子的失踪有关？
Buddy and his kid disappearing?
我觉得这种事从来没发生过
I think this kind of thing doesn't happen here.
你告诉他妻子了？
You told his wife?
警长 我们收到报告说
Sheriff, we have a report
16区下水道有小规模煤气爆炸
of a small gas explosion in the sewer under 16th.
- 你收到了吗？- 明白 分派员
- Do you copy? - Roger, Dispatch.
- 通知消防队 - 我们在那儿跟他们汇合
- Notify the fire department - I'll meet 'em there.
马上 警长 分派员结束通话
Right away, Sheriff. Dispatch out.
你需要帮忙吗？
You want some help?
我不知道 达拉斯
I don't know, Dallas.
来吧
Come on.
我坐到后面
I'll ride in the back.
内特？
Nate?
Nate?!
内特 你跑哪儿去了？
Nate, where are you?
什么？
What?
瑞奇
Ricky.
嘿
Hey.
那么 呃
So, uh…
我们怎么进去？
how do we get in?
放学后我复制了钥匙
I taped the lock after class.
我不能决定该穿哪件泳衣 所以
I couldn't decide on which suit I wanted to wear, so…
现在 你告诉我
Now… you tell me…
你看的是我 还是钟？
…are you looking at me or the clock?
过来
Come here.
哦 天啊
Oh, my God.
你觉得你在做什么 杰丝？
What do you think you're doing, Jess?
戴尔 滚出去
Dale, get out of here.
记住我的话 瑞奇
Just remember, Ricky…
这个小婊子知道每件事 都是我教的
I taught this little slut everything she knows.
- 不 瑞奇 - 住手
- No, Ricky… - stop it!
- 住手 - 戴尔 住手
- Stop it! - Dale, stop it!
住手 他会淹死的
Stop it! He's drowning!
放开我
Get off me.
那是什么鬼东西？
What the hell was that?
哦 上帝
Oh, my God.
上帝 赶快从水里出来
Oh, my God, get out of the water.
- 出去 - 杰西 跑
- Get out! - Jesse, go!
跑
Go!
哦 上帝 从水池里出来
Oh, my God, get out of the pool!
杰丝 跑
Jess, run!
哦 天呐
Oh, my God!
跑 跑
Go! Go!
你觉得他死了吗？
Do you think he's dead?
你为什么不回去看看？
Why don't you go back and find out?
不
No.
这边
Here!
窗户
Window!
妈的 妈的
Shit! Oh, shit!
啊 救救我
Aah, help me!
加油
Come on!
救命 啊
Help me, aah!
瑞奇 快走
Ricky, come on!
走
Go!
警长 核电站发生了一起爆炸
Sheriff we have a 10- 80 at the nuclear power plant.
收到 我们在十分钟后赶到
Roger that. We'll be there in 10 minutes.
好的 警长 国家安全局也被通知到了
10- 4, Sheriff. County and state have been advised as well.
打算告诉我发生了什么吗？
Wanna tell me what the hell's goin' on?
核电站发生了一起爆炸
There's been an explosion at the plant.
今天变的更有意思了
Well, this day keeps getting better.
爸爸 爸爸
Daddy, Daddy!
- 爸爸 - 嘿
- Daddy! - Hey.
怎么了？
What is it?
那东西在外面
It was outside the window.
什么？
What?
一个怪物
It was a monster.
哦 到这来
Oh, come here.
过来
Come here.
知道吗 我像你这么大的时候
You know, when I was your age…
我也经常做这种噩梦
I used to have these awful nightmares.
我看到了
I saw it.
是真的
It was real.
看 没有怪物
See? No monster.
蒂姆
Tim!
爸爸
Daddy!
Dad!
我们得跑
We have to go.
快点
Come on!
爸爸
Daddy!
大火吞噬了整个核电站
The fire spread through the whole plant.
他们必须手动关闭核反应装置
They have to shut down the reactors manually.
收到
Roger that.
分派员 我们得疏散整个镇
Dispatch, we have to evacuate the entire town.
请求科罗拉多州国民警卫队援助
Call the National Guard in Colorado Springs for assistance.
完毕
Over.
好的
10- 4.
上帝啊
Jesus Christ.
- 警长 - 是
- Sheriff. - Yeah.
你得来听听这个
I think you should hear about this.
达拉斯
Dallas!
好吧 非常感谢
All right, thanks a lot.
瑞奇 你跑到这个鬼地方干嘛来了？
Ricky, what the hell you doing here?
有东西追我们 我不知道发生了什么
Something came after us… I don't know what happened.
- 你说「有东西」是什么意思 - 我们一直跑到这里来
- What do you mean something… - We ran all the way here.
慢一点 什么东西追你们？
Slow down. What came after you?
- 我不知道 - 你们当时在哪儿？
- I don't know! - Where were you?
我们在学校里 马克 他 他死了
We were at the school. Mark… h- he's dead…
我想它们也杀了尼克
and I think they got Nick, too.
是什么东西？
What was it?
瑞奇
Ricky!
我不知道
I don't know.
打电话求助
Call in help.
必须让什么人知道这些
Somebody's got to know about this.
艾迪
Eddie.
分派员 我们的支援呢？
Dispatch, where's that backup?
分派员 回答
Dispatch, come in.
我们走 离开这个鬼地方
Let's go, let's get the hell out of here.
凯瑞？
Carrie?
断电了
The power's out.
凯瑞？
Carrie?
凯瑞 是你吗？
Carrie, are you over…
哦
Oh!
哦 天呐
Oh, my God.
救命
Help me!
我们得一直跑 宝贝
We have to keep running, baby.
离开这个鬼地方
Let's get outta here!
不 不 不
No, no! No!
妈妈 我们扔下了他
Mommy! We left him!
安静
Quiet. Shh.
过来 过来
Come on, come on.
妈妈 我害怕
Mommy, I'm scared.
没事 没事 我们会没事的
Shh. It's okay. It's okay. We're gonna be okay.
你见到了吗？
Did you see one?
我也是
Me, too.
妈妈 你为什么要丢下爸爸？
Mommy, why did you leave Daddy?
让她闭嘴
Shut her up!
把烟掐灭 趴下
Hey. Put the cigarette out and get down.
去你的 我可不藏在这等死
Fuck you. I'm not gonna die hiding.
去你的
Fuck you.
- 你会把我们害死的 - 我想回家
- You're gonna get us all killed. - I wanna go home!
- 让她闭嘴 让她闭嘴 - 我想找爸爸
- Shut her up. Shut her up. - I wanna see Daddy!
让她闭嘴 不然我向上帝发誓
Shut her the fuck up, or I swear to God…
我可不觉得警察局是个好主意
I don't think the police station is such a hot idea.
你想让我做什么？
What do you want me to do?
我们不知道我们对付的是什么
We don't know what we're dealing with.
快点
Come on.
小心
Look out!
警长
Sheriff.
- 达西？- 艾迪
- Darcy? - Eddie.
达西 怎么了 你在干什么？
Darcy, what happened? What are you doing?
- 厨房里 凯瑞的胃 - 什么？
- At the diner. Carrie's stomach. - What?
- 什么？- 到处都是血
- Shh. What? - There was so much blood.
她的胃 没了
Her stomach… it was gone.
她死了 她死了
She's dead! She's dead…
瑞奇 把她扶进去
Ricky, get her inside.
让她进去
Get her in.
艾迪 不停地死人
Eddie, people are dying.
我们需要枪
We need guns.
国民警卫队很快就会过来
The National Guard'll be here soon.
还不够快
Not soon enough.
不敢相信我让你这样做
Can't believe I'm letting you do this.
这个计划很蠢
This plan is stupid.
我们得马上离开镇子
Let's just leave town now.
因为我们没有武器
'Cause we're not going to make it out of town
就走不了 傻鸟
without weapons, dickhead.
你说话太蠢了 戴尔 闭嘴
You're too stupid to talk, Dale. |Shut up.
枪在哪儿？
Where are the guns?
跟着我
Follow me.
在这里
Here they are.
戴尔 找个袋子来
Dale, grab some bags.
杰西 把枪上膛
Jesse, load them up.
艾迪 你有电把那东西点亮？
Eddie, you got power on that thing?
是啊 我需要光
Yeah, I just need some light.
走 走 走
Go! Go! Go!
第一小队 封锁这个区域
Ground One, secure the area.
建立隔离带 掩护第二小队
Set up perimeter, provide cover for Ground Two.
收到 零到六号出发
Roger, Zero- 6 out.
走 走 走
Move! Move! Move!
报告情况
Report status.
第一小队已建好隔离带
Ground One has secured perimeter.
第二小队已建好隔离带
Ground Two has secured perimeter.
警长马若勒斯呼叫国民警卫队 请回答
This is Sheriff Morales for the National Guard. Come in.
重复 警长马若勒斯呼叫国民警卫队
Repeat, Sheriff Morales for the National Guard.
请回答
Come in.
我是国民警卫队 89师
This is Lieutenant Woods, 89th Troop Command…
伍得中尉
Colorado National Guard.
请讲 警长
Go ahead, Sheriff.
你的位置在哪里 中尉 完毕
What's your location, Lieutenant? Over.
我们在干道上
We're on Main Street.
听着 中尉 我不知道
Listen, Lieutenant, I don't know
你们的人要面对什么
what your men are walking into…
但是我们的情况变得越来越糟糕
but our situation is getting worse.
中尉 请回答 你还在吗？
Lieutenant, come in. Are you there?
我们有个人失踪了
We have a missing man.
等一下 警长
Hold on, Sheriff.
- 射击 - 我们遭遇了
- Fire! - We've got contact!
- 停止射击 - 我们中埋伏了
- Hold your fire! - It's a fucking ambush!
防御 九点钟
Fender, 9:00!
究竟是他妈的怎么回事？
What the hell's going on out there?!
我们遭遇了
We've got contact!
撤退 重复 撤退
Fall back! I repeat, fall back!
中尉
Lieutenant!
中尉 你在吗？
Lieutenant, are you there?
中尉 请回答 你在吗？
Lieutenant, come in. Are you there?
我们逃不了了 是吧？
We're not going to make it, are we?
别开枪 随便拿
Don't shoot! Take what you want!
我不该为了每小时六圆两角被杀
I'm not getting killed for no $6.25 an hour.
我们被攻击了
We've been attacked.
恐怖分子袭击吉那森了？
Terrorists hit Gunnison?
早告诉你他们有天会的
Told you they would one day.
你们是什么人 喝高了？
What are you guys, stoned?
拿把枪
Grab some rifles.
你看到那个了吗？
You see that?
快点 茉莉
Hurry up, Molly.
Hurry, Molly.
有人吗？
Hello?!
Hello?
你受伤了吗？
Are you hurt?
进来吧
Come on in.
她在这儿会安全的
She'll be safe here.
罗森医生请到2号急救室
Dr. Lossen to O.R. 2, stat.
使劲压住伤口
Keep pressure on that.
再来一升
Another liter.
等一下
Hold up.
明显的外伤
Apparently got a carotid.
直接带他去急救室
Take him straight to Trauma.
慢一点
Easy now.
上来吧
Here you go.
黄色警报 黄色警报
Code yellow, code yellow.
所有非轮班医护人员马上到特别监护室报道
All non- shift medical personnel report to Critical Care.
嗨
Hi.
灯什么时候重新打开的？
When are the lights going back on?
在电源恢复之前 我们起用紧急发电机
We're on emergency generators until the power's restored.
哦 上帝
Oh, God.
哦 我想我的羊水破了
Oh, I think my water just broke.
好的
Okay.
我去找个医生
I'll find a doctor.
不
No!
嘿
Hey.
你们两个都在发抖
You two look pretty shaken up.
今天晚上对她来说很不容易
Hasn't been an easy night for her.
那你怎么样？
And what about you?
我会活着
I'll live.
好吧
Okay.
我们5分钟后出发
We're leaving in five minutes.
谢谢你
Thank you.
他在哪儿？
Where is he?
把枪给我 把枪给我
Give me the gun. Give me the gun!
跟我来
Come on!
妈妈
Mommy!
回去 是个陷阱
Turn back! It's a trap!
是陷阱 陷阱
It's a trap! It's a trap!
什么鬼玩意儿？
What the fuck?
- 跑 跑 跑 - 跑
- Go! Go! Go! - Go!
茉莉 快点 跑 跑 茉莉
Molly, come on, run! Run, Molly!
所有人 跑 跑 到外面去
Everyone, go, go! Out the front!
操他妈的
Fuck this!
打死这狗日的
Shoot the fucking thing!
- 达拉斯 - 那是什么东西？
- Dallas… - What was that thing?
怎么？
What?
这不可能
That's not possible.
妈的
Shit.
出问题了
Something's wrong.
检查下其他房间
Check the other rooms!
怎么回事？
What is…
- 快点 对 - 跑
- Come on, yeah… - Go…
跑 孩子 跑 别停下
Go, baby, go! Keep running.
一直往前 一直往前
Straight ahead. Straight ahead.
发生了什么？
What the hell?
这就是我们的救援？
This is our help?!
出了什么鬼事 艾迪？
What the fuck is going on, Eddie?!
尸体都跑到哪儿去了？
Where the hell are the bodies?
哦 它们会把我们全杀了的
Oh, they're gonna kill us all!
我们还没死
We're not dead yet.
也许还有武器和装备我们能用
There may be weapons and equipment we can still use.
电台
Radio.
国民警卫队 请回答
National Guard, come in.
重复 国民警卫队 请回答
Repeat… any National Guard unit, come in.
我是美国军队史迪文上校
This is Colonel Stevens, U.S. Army.
表明你们的身份
Identify yourself.
警长 艾迪·马若勒斯
Sheriff Eddie Morales.
吉那森 罗拉多州
Gunnison, Colorado.
你必须帮我们 上校
You have to help us, Colonel.
这里有某种异形
There's some kind of infestation
如果我们不马上得到帮助 我们就都会死
and if we don't get help soon, there won't be any of us left.
军队的疏散计划是什么？
What's the army's evacuation plan?
上校？
Colonel?
上校 我们需要立即疏散
Colonel, we need immediate evac.
警长 所有的地面通道
Sheriff, all ground routes
都不安全
have been compromised.
30分钟之后 吉莉安广场
There is an airlift in 30 minutes
会有一次空中救援
from Gilliam Circle.
确认：空中救援 吉莉安广场
Confirm: airlift, Gilliam Circle.
我们20分钟后到达
We'll be there in 20 minutes.
但那是在市中心
But that's right in the center of town.
我们会赶到的 上校
We'll be there, Colonel.
你是什么鬼玩意儿？
What the fuck are you?
所有人 到车厢里去
Everyone, get in the Striker!
我来开车
I'll drive.
上车 快 快 快
Get up, go, go, go, go.
你确定你能开这玩意儿？
You sure you can drive that thing?
好吧 我来负责拿枪
All right, I'll get on the gun.
别打偏
Don't miss.
别撞车
Don't crash.
抓紧了
Hold on!
为什么停下来？
Why are we stopping?
这没一点道理
It doesn't make any sense.
吉莉安广场在小镇的正中央
Gilliam Circle is right in the center of town.
我们会被那些东西包围的
We'll be surrounded by those things.
- 等下 你在说什么？- 我认为上校在骗我们
- Wait a second… what are you saying? - I think the colonel was lying.
真荒谬
That's crazy.
政府从来不对人民撒谎
The government doesn't lie to people.
军队会首先考虑污染
The army thinks about containment first.
他们不能冒险让情况变得更糟糕
They can't risk this getting any worse.
救援就在几公里以外的地方 他们正在等我们
Help is a few miles down that road and they're waiting for us.
如果你不想带我们去 我带
Now, if you won't drive us there, I will.
艾迪 如果她是对的
Eddie, if she's right, the only thing
等着我们的就是更多的异形
down that road are more of those things.
你没有认真考虑这件事
You're not seriously considering this.
我考虑如何让我们活下去
I'm considering whatever keeps us alive.
就是逃出这个镇子
Which means getting out of this town.
镇里只有两架直升机
There are only two helicopters in town…
但一架在机场
but one's at the airport.
不 太远了 我们不可能到那儿
No, it's too far. We'll never make it.
另一架在医院
The other one's at the hospital.
医院的人可能用它逃生了
The people at the hospital probably used it to get out.
但那是我们的机会
That's a chance we have to take.
如果你们错了 直升机飞走了
If you're wrong and the helicopter's gone…
我们就都死了
we're all dead.
如果我对了 他们跟着你 也是死路一条
If I'm right, they're dead if they follow you.
有辆卡车开过来了
There's a truck coming.
在吉莉安广场
There will be
将会有紧急疏散
an emergency evacuation from Gilliam Circle.
医疗救护和空中救援
Medical care and airlift…
警长 你在这儿干什么？
Sheriff, what the hell are you doing in there?
别操心这个了
Never mind that.
你们要去空中救援点？
You guys heading to the airlift?
是的
Yeah.
好 跟着我们 没多少时间了
Okay, follow us. We don't have much time.
好了 听着
All right, listen up.
每个人都必须马上做出决定
Everybody's got to choose right now.
我们乘坦克 去医院
I'm going to the hospital with the tank.
我们只需要跑到镇中心
We all need to go to the center of town.
- 没错 - 我跟着我哥哥
- That's right. - I'm going with my brother.
- 我和你一起 - 我进坦克去
- I'm with you. - I'm going in the tank.
达拉斯 别这么做
Dallas, don't do this.
她错了
She's wrong.
不管是不是兄弟 他错了
And brother or not, he's wrong.
你会害死他们的
You're gonna get them killed!
我们没时间了 警长 我们必须马上出发
We're running out of time, Sheriff… we gotta move now.
等下
Hold on!
我们跟你一起去
We're coming with you!
等等
Wait.
保重
Take care.
我希望我们都错了
I hope we're both wrong.
医疗救护和空中救援
Medical care and airlift…
出发
Let's go!
在吉莉安广场
There will be an emergency evacuation
将会有紧急疏散
from Gilliam Circle.
医疗救护和空中救援 提供给所有居民
Medical care and airlift will be provided for all residents.
我没有救任何人
I didn't help anybody.
我太害怕了
I was too scared.
我就看着他们死
I just watched them die.
好了 穿上这个
All right, put these on.
你也是
You, too.
好了 听着
All right, listen…
不管在里面发生什么事
whatever happens inside…
唯一不能受伤的是凯莉 明白吗？
the only person that can't get hurt is Kelly, all right?
我们都保护凯莉
We all protect Kelly.
这是哪出 泰坦尼克？
What is this, the Titanic?
去他妈的妇女孩子先走那一套 伙计
Screw the women and children first shit, man.
听着 白痴 除非你会开直升机
Look, asshole, unless you can fly the helicopter…
不然就闭嘴 我们走
shut the fuck up. Let's go.
哦 天呐
Oh, Jesus.
也许他们都走了
Maybe they've all gone.
哦 上帝 不
Oh, God, no!
打死他妈的
Fucking shoot it!
杰西 不 等等
Jesse, no, wait!
跑 快
Move, now!
杰西
Jesse!
不 等等
No, wait!
瑞奇
Ricky!
瑞奇 等等
Ricky, wait!
狗娘养的
Motherfucker!
瑞奇
Ricky!
走吧
Come on.
快点 起来
Come on, get up.
你不会死的
You're gonna make it.
我们得马上走 现在
We have to go… now!
来
Come on…
快点
Come on!
走 走 走 走 走
Go! Go, go, go, go!
乔
Joe!
所有人都在吗？
Is this everybody?
这是所有活着的人
This is all that's left.
你听到了什么？
What have you heard?
空中救援马上就到
The airlift will be here soon.
安全
Clear!
跟上
Come on!
走 走 你没事吧？
Go, go! You all right?
过来 茉莉
Come here, Molly.
跑 跑 跟着你妈
Go! Go! Follow your mom!
快点
Come on!
所有人 快点
Everyone, move!
跑 茉莉
Run, Molly!
快点
Come on!
达拉斯
Dallas!
我在试
I'm trying!
你打算用那东西？
Are you gonna shoot that thing?
等一等
Hang on!
我们走
Let's go!
抱稳她了？
You got her?
卧倒
Get down!
史迪文上校 这里是吉那森镇
Colonel Stevens, this is Gunnison County
请求疏散 完毕
requesting status on evac! Over!
上校 空中救援在哪儿？
Colonel, where's the airlift?
警长 我们还有10公里
Sheriff, we are ten miles out.
原地待命 完毕
Hold your position. Over.
上校 我们在这里 完毕
Colonel, we're here. Over.
上帝拯救我们
God help us all.
好了 离开这儿 马上
All right, get out of here… now.
我来争取点时间
I'm gonna buy us some time.
我不离开你
I'm not leaving you.
上直升机
Get to the chopper!
你不必这样做 达拉斯
You don't have to do this, Dallas.
马上 去 去
Now! Go! Go!
放马过来 狗娘养的
Come on, you motherfuckers!
好 走
Okay, go!
凯莉 趴下
Kelly! Get down!
走 走 走
Go! Go! Go!
嘿 这边
Hey, over here!
快点
Come on.
好了 走
Okay, go!
操
Fuck!
嘿 你过来
Hey, come on over here!
快点
Come on!
干你娘的
Fuck you!
我们不能丢下他不管
We're not leaving without him!
我们必须得走
We have to go.
他会赶来的
He'll make it!
死
Die!
出发
Let's go!
妈妈？
Mommy?
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes!
- 抓紧 - 妈妈
- Hang on! - Mommy!
达拉斯？
Dallas?
哦 天呐
Oh, Jesus.
嘿 你还好吧？瑞奇？
Hey, you all right? Ricky?
- 是的 - 使劲按 甜心
- Yeah. - Press harder, honey.
放下武器
Drop your weapons!
你们这群王八蛋杀了整个镇子的人
You bastards killed the entire town.
我们只是服从命令
We're just following orders.
放下武器
Now, put down your weapons.
我弟弟需要救护
We need a medic for my brother.
救援马上就到
Medevac is inbound.
收集所有武器 建立隔离带
Secure any weapons, and let's set up a perimeter!
出发 快点
Let's go! Move it!
我想我跟你说过别撞车
Thought I told you not to crash.
妈妈？
Mommy?
怪物都死了吗？
Are the monsters gone?
都死了
They're gone.
这个世界还没准备好接受这种武器
The world isn't ready for this technology.
但这不是给我们的世界准备的 不是吗 尤塔尼女士？
But this isn't for our world, is it, Ms. Yutani?